Guide to the Jim Graham papers, 1961-2015 MS2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jim Graham/D.C. Council records, 1961-2015; 1998-2014; MS2013 Series 2
  - Photographs, 1998-2014; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Photos: Jim Graham in Pride Parade, undated (Box 3A, Folder 11)
    - Photos: Christmas Event for LGBT Friends of Mayor Anthony Williams, undated (Box 3A, Folder 12)
    - Photos: Used for Jim Graham Website, undated (Box 3A, Folder 13)
    - Photos: Jim Graham at Washington, D.C. Vietnamese Community Center, undated (Box 3A, Folder 14)
    - Photos: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3A, Folder 15)
    - Photo Printouts: Jim Graham at Public Events, undated (Box 3A, Folder 16)
    - Photos: Jim Graham at 1998 Campaign Events, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 1)
    - Photos: Miscellaneous campaign events, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 2)
    - Photos: Medicaid Community Attendant Services and Supports Act (Micassa) Event, D.C. Council Meeting, 2001; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 3)
    - Photos: Marriage Equality Act Signing, 2009 December 18; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 4)
    - Work of art featuring Jim Graham, 2013; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 5)
    - Photos: Fortieth Anniversary of D.C.'s Home Rule Charter, 2014 October 24; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 6)
    - Photos: Miscellaneous unidentified D.C. Council events, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 7)
    - Photos: Historic Images of Ward 1 [1/2], undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 8)
    - Photos: Historic Images of Ward 1 [2/2], undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 9)
    - Photo album: Miscellaneous events, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 10)
    - Photo album: Miscellaneous events, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 10A, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Mayoral Inauguration, 1999 January 02; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 14A, Folder 6)
    - CD-ROM: Photos from the Anacostia Light Rail Ground Breaking, 2004 November 13; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 14A, Folder 7)
    - CD-ROM: Photos from the New York Ave-Florida Ave-Gallaudet University Station Opening, 2004 November 20; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 14A, Folder 8)
    - CD-ROM: Photos from the Dalai Lama's visit to Booker T. Washington Public Charter School, 2005 November 10; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 14A, Folder 9)
    - CD-ROM: Jim Graham photos, 2006; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 14A, Folder 10)
  - Oversized, 1999-2009; Series 2 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains items that are too large to be housed with the rest of the collection. The items include posters and banners relating to Jim Graham's time as a D.C. City Council member.
    - Poster: Dedication of National World War II Memorial (signed), 2004 May 29 (Box 4A, Folder 2)
    - Poster: "Life preserver.", 2009 December (Box 4A, Folder 7)
    - Poster: Gelman Library reception for Jim Graham, 1999 September 23 (Box 4A, Folder 15)
    - Poster: Jim Graham caricature, 2003 December (Box 4A, Folder 18)
    - Pennant Banner: New York Ave - Florida Ave - Gallaudet U Metrorail station opening, 2004 November 20 (Box 5A, Folder 16)
    - Poster: John A. Wilson, undated (Box 5A, Folder 17)
      Poster mounted on foamboard. Printout of unidentified man's face attached with tape.
    - Poster: John A. Wilson (portrait), undated (Box 5A, Folder 18)
      Poster mounted on foamboard.
  - Campaign materials, 1997-2010; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains correspondence, reports, polling information, research, and advertising material relating to Jim Graham's first campaign for Councilmember of Ward 1 for the District of Columbia, as well as materials from his subsequent re-election campaigns from 2002 to 2010. Graham also ran for re-election in 2014, but was defeated. The materials date from 1997 to 2010. There may be related materials, especially for Graham's subsequent re-election campaigns, in Series 2 Subseries 1.
    This subseries is arranged chronologically starting with Graham's first campaign in 1998. There may be related materials, especially for Graham's subsequent re-election campaigns, in Series 2 Subseries 1.
    - 1998 Campaign for D.C. Council, 1997-1998; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 1)
    - 1998 Campaign for D.C. Council, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 2)
    - 1998 Campaign for D.C. Council, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 3)
    - 1998 Campaign for D.C. Council, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 4)
    - 1998 Campaign for D.C. Council, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 5)
    - 1998 Campaign materials folder, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 6)
    - Brochure 8C [1998 Campaign materials], 1997-1998; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 7)
    - Platform [1998 Campaign materials], MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 8)
    - PBC Board of Directors Monthly Meeting 03/20/98, 1998 March 30; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11A, Folder 9)
    - Jim Direct Mail [and Campaign expenses], 1998; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 1)
    - 1998 Campaign advertising materials, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 2)
    - 1998 Campaign finance materials [1/2], MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 3)
    - 1998 Campaign finance materials [2/2], MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 4)
    - Primary Election Day folder, September 15, 1998, 1998 September 15; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 5)
    - 1998 D.C. Council Primary and General Election results, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 6)
    - Photos: Jim Graham Campaign, 1998; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 7)
    - 2004 Potential At-Large Councilmember Campaign, MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 8)
    - Councilmember Jim Graham Cross-Tabs from a Survey of 400 2004 Likely Democratic Primary Election Voters in Washington, DC, 2004 March; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 9)
    - 2006 Re-Election Campaign, 2002-2006; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12A, Folder 10)
    - 2010 Re-Election Campaign, 2009-2010; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 13A, Folder 1)
    - Draft of Dick Morris' "The New Prince" [1/2], undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 13A, Folder 2)
    - Draft of Dick Morris' "The New Prince" [2/2], undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 13A, Folder 3)
    - Audio cassette tapes: Jim Graham Campaign interviews, 1998; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 14A, Folder 11)
    - Audio cassette tapes: Consensus Communications, Friends Jim Graham, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 14A, Folder 12)
    - CD-ROM: The Politics Hour, Ward One Debate, WAMU 88.5 FM, 2010 August 20; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 14A, Folder 13)
- Personal papers, 1972-2014; 1984-1999; MS2013 Series 3
  This series contains previously restricted material donated by Jim Graham. Included are personal correspondence, Whitman-Walker correspondence and other material, printed materials and clippings, and personal materials from before and after Jim Graham's Council years, dating from the early 1970s until 2014.
  Arranged into 5 subseries: Personal correspondence, Whitman-Walker materials, Pamphlets and printed materials, Clippings, and Early career and post-Council materials.
  - Personal correspondence and subject files, 1986-2005; Series 3 Subseries 1
    This subseries containes personal correspondence written to Jim Graham. It includes letters, postcards, invitations and other related materials dating from 1986-2005.
    Arranged chronologically by date.
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 19891994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Council), 1998-2000; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Council), 1998-2000; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Council), 2000; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2002; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2004-2006; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2005; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Lessons from Thanks drafts, Circa 1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Van Gloede, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Council materials, Address book, Circa 1990-2000; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Whitman Walker Clinic materials, 1984-2009; 1984-1999; Series 3 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains materials pertaining to Jim Graham's work as the director of the Whitman Walker Clinic and his long-time advocacy for HIV/AIDS and LGBT issues. Included are memos and other documents; printed materials; correspondence; video cassettes; event t-shirts; and other related materials dating from 1984 to around 2009.
    The majority of the subseries is arranged chronologically by date, with the exception of the video cassettes, t-shirts, and posters, which have been processed but not individually cataloged.
    - Whitman Walker Material, 1984-1992; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Whitman Walker, 1985-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1985-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Whitman Walker Clinic Material, 1986-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1986-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1986-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1986-1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1986-1992; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Elizabeth Taylor, Circa 1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Whitman Walker, 1993-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Whitman Walker, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Whitman Walker, 1995-1996; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Whitman Walker, 1995-1996; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Whitman Walker, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Whitman Walker, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Whitman Walker Material, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Whitman Walker Material, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Whitman Walker Other, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Whitman Walker, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Gene Frey Awards, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Whitman Walker, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Whitman Walker, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Whitman Walker Material, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Whitman Walker, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Whitman Walker Materials, 1991-1997; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Whitman-Walker, 1984-1993; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Whitman-Walker, 1994-1999; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Video cassettes, circa 1980s - circa 1990s (Box 26)
      Please note: this box is processed, but not individually cataloged. Most of the cassettes have AIDS or Whitman Walker-related recordings.
    - T-shirts, circa 1980s - circa 1990s (Box 27)
      Please note: this box is processed, but not individually cataloged. Most of the t-shirts are AIDS or Whitman Walker-related.
    - T-shirts, circa 1980s - circa 1990s (Box 28)
      Please note: this box is processed, but not individually cataloged. Most of the t-shirts are AIDS or Whitman Walker-related. (This box contains 1989 Washington, DC AIDS Walk t-shirts with a logo designed by Keith Harring.)
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 1)
      Please note: this tube is processed, but not individually cataloged. Most of the posters are AIDS or Whitman Walker-related.
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 2)
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 3)
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 4)
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 5)
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 6)
    - Posters, circa 1980s - circa 2000s (Tube 7)
  - Pamphlets and printed material, 1989-2006; Series 3 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains pamphlets, programs, flyers and other printed materials amassed by Jim Graham dating from 1989-2006.
    - Pamphlets, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Programs, Pamplets, 1988-1991; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets, 1989-1993; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 1993-1994; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Programs, Pamplets, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets, 1993-1995; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Program, Pamphlets, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, Programs, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Programs, Pamplets, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets, Programs, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Programs, miscellaneous materials, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Programs, Memorial Services, 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Services, 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, Miscellaneous materials, 1998-1999; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Programs, Memorial material, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, Publications, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Programs, Pamphlets, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, 2004; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets, 2005; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Program, Publication, Memorial Materials, 2006; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1986-1999; Series 3 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains newspaper clippings amassed by Jim Graham dating from 1986-1999.
    - Clippings, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1985-1986; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1993-1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1994-1997; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1994-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1995; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1997; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (1/4], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Clippings [2/4], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Clippings [3/4], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Clippings [4/4], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1998-1999; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Clippings [1/3], 1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Clippings [2/3], 1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Clippings [3/3], 1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Early career and post-Council materials, 1972-2014; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5
    - Wisconsin Law Review, Volume 1921, number 2, 1972; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - "Laws' Labor Lost: Judicial Politics in the Progressive Era," James M. Graham, Wisconsin Law Review, Volume 1972, number 2, 1972, MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - VHK [Victor H. Kramer and Jim Graham] [1/2], circa 1970s - circa 1990s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - VHK [Victor H. Kramer and Jim Graham] [2/2], circa 1970s - circa 1990s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - I [Regulation and Government Oversight] [1/2], 1982, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - I [Regulation and Government Oversight] [1/2], 1982, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - IA [Regulation and Government Oversight] [1/2], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - IA [Regulation and Government Oversight] [2/2], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - IB [Regulation and Government Oversight] [1/2], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - IB [Regulation and Government Oversight] [2/2], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - II [Regulation and Government Oversight] [1/2], circa 1970s - circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - II [Regulation and Government Oversight] [2/2], circa 1970s - circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - IIa [Regulation and Government Oversight], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - III [Regulation and Government Oversight] [1/2], 1980-1981, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight [1/2], 1978, 1981, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight [2/2], 1978, 1981, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight [1/2], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight [2/2], circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight [1/2], 1981, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight [2/2], 1981, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight course materials [1/2], undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight course materials [2/2], undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Regulation and Government Oversight, 1978, 1980, 1982, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Government operations and oversight, circa 1980s; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Personal materials, 1977-1978, 1983; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Personal materials, 1986, 1988, 1991, 2013-2014, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Photos: Miscellaneous, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Photos: Miscelleanous, 2006, undated; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Photo: Unidentified, 1979; MS2013 Series 3 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 1)